GORDON WATTS

UNITY GENERALIST

GORDONTWATTS@GMAIL.COM

BACKGROUND

A Unity Engine Generalist with 4+ years background in programming experience, and 1 year of experience working with Unity. Technical minded and problem solving oriented, I am proficient at bug fixing, creating systems for games, as well as gameplay programming. Developed a handful of Unity Projects, with proven proficiency in GitHub, Visual Studio, and the Unity Game Engine. I am very much a team player and excel in a team setting.

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2021 - present

Unity Class Instructor at Crafting Education Academy

- Presenting knowledge of Unity tools and features to an audience of children.
- Taking a child friendly approach to teaching programming via Unity Bolt.
- Constructing small prototypes and game demos to enable active learning and problem solving.

Jun 2018 - Dec 2019

Shift Leader at Five Guys

- Lead a team through leveraging interpersonal skills and team building exercises.
- Assisted customers with queries using product knowledge.
- Communicated any shift problems to immediate supervisor.
- Worked flexible schedule, including evening and weekend hours.
- Coached employees and maintained physical presence on shift
- Monitored quality and quantity of output of production lines during course of shift.
- Delivered sales through friendly and efficient customer service.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

 1+ year of experience in Unity making many prototypes and a handful of small games.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Digital Media Computer Science Minor Mathematics Minor Orlando, FL 3.5 GPA, expected graduation May 2024

EASTERN FLORIDA STATE COLLEGE

Associate of the Arts (A.A.) Melbourne, FL Graduated May 2019

KEY SKILLS

- MANAGEMENT
- GAME DESIGN

TOOLS

- C# LANGUAGE
- C LANGUAGE
- UNITY GAME ENGINE

AWARDS

DEAN'S LIST EFSC 2016-2019

- 4+ years background in programming in a variety of languages including C#, C, Java, and Python.
- Proficiency in tools such as GitHub, Trello, Visual Studio.

EXTRACURRICULAR / PROJECTS

- UCF Game Dev Knights Event Director 21 22
- Game Terra Nova
 This was my first Unity game completed in a team setting.
 With it originally starting off in a Game Jam, my team members and I decided to complete the game and soon fully released it on the GameJolt platform.
 https://gamejolt.com/games/terranova/592282
- Game Space Invaders Clone
 This is my first game project made from scratch. Took a few weeks to make, but in that time, I learned so much about the game making process. Also challenged my programming skills, and my knowledge of the engine I used, Unity. https://dstroid.itch.io/space-invaders-clone

REFERENCES

Available on request.